# Thanh Nguyen

© San Jose, California ♠ thanhnguyenhm.me ☒ nguyenhm.thanh@ gmail.com

Born 10 Jan 1992, Vietnamese citizen, United States resident, female, single.

I'm studying Computer Science and planning to transfer to a 4-year university in the University of California system in Fall 2017.

## **Education**

**De Anza - Foothill Community College**, Cupertino, California, major in Computer
Science

Jun 2014-present

Foreign Trade University, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, major in International Business Aug 2010-Jun 2013

### Coursework

Programming Methodologies in C++

Object-Oriented Programming and Software Design in JAVA

Advanced Data Structures and Algorithms

MIPS Assembly Language Programming

Computer Architecture and Organization

Single Variable Calculus

Multivariable Calculus

Linear Algebra

**Differential Equations** 

Discrete Mathematics

# **Experience**

Administrative Assistant , DT Foods, Santa Clara, California Sep 2014-Present

Freelancer: translator English to Vietnamese, data entry, web design

Dec 2010-Apr 2014

**Teaching Assistant** in Math, Kumon Vietnam Mar 2011-Dec 2012

Private ESL Tutor Jan 2011-Jul 2012

#### Skills

C++, Java, MIPS Assembly

basic HTML, CSS, markdown, LTFX

Windows, Linux, Git, Microsoft Dynamics NAV, Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop

86 WPM typist, detailed-oriented, fast learner

## Languages

Mother tongue: **Vietnamese**, Fluent: **English**, Intermediate: **Japanese**